They have forty-five minutes to save the world. They need forty-six.
Big Trouble is a action, comedy, thriller film directed by Barry Sonnenfeld.
The story of how a mysterious suitcase brings together, and changes, the lives of a divorced dad, an unhappy
housewife, two hitmen, a pair of street thugs, two love struck teens, two FBI men and a psychedelic toad.
Based on Pulitzer Prize-winning humorist Dave Barry's
best-selling first novel, "Big Trouble."
Eliot Arnold, played by Tim Allen.
Anna Herk, played by Rene Russo.
Matt Arnold, played by Ben Foster.
Puggy, played by Jason Lee.
Arthur Herk, played by Stanley Tucci.
Henry Desalvo, played by Dennis Farina.
Big Trouble is a 2002 American black comedy film based
on the novel Big Trouble by Dave Barry.
It was directed by Barry Sonnenfeld and featured a large cast including Tim Allen and Rene Russo with Dennis
Farina, Zooey Deschanel, Sofia Vergara, in her film debut, and Jason Lee in supporting roles.
Like much of Dave Barry's fiction, it follows a diverse group of people through a series of
extremely strange and humorous situations against the backdrop of Miami.
The film was a box-office bomb, and received mixed critical reception.
The film explores themes of taunting, gadfly, dubious, frustrated.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending and intense.